

## **Profile**

Data Analyst/help desk analyst/programmer with 3 plus years of experience looking to utilize skills I have learned over the past several years to help others become more productive, enhance user experiences, and provide value to the business and their partners. I am a motivated self-starter, actively working to improve my skills and open to learning new technologies. You can view some the projects I have worked on in the past on my online portfolio found at:

https://mr-bland.github.io/Portfolio-DB/

## **Contact**

PHONE:

864 363 7021

**EMAIL:** 

daniel.byrd2@charter.net

LINKED-IN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/danielbyrd-090004170/

**LOCATION** 

Taylors, SC

Willing to work remote

## **Key Skills**

Programmer Analyst Help Desk Analyst Web Designer Digital Artist

# **Daniel Byrd**

Data Analyst, Programmer, Designer, Help Desk Analyst

#### **Work Experience**

#### Service Desk Analyst at Pomeroy

(January 2020 – October 2023)

- Assisted UMB Bank with many technical issues from programs/systems not responding or operating correctly, to account unlocks and password resets. Completed a combined total of 12,000+ calls on various systems and issues.
- Constructed a HTML helper website designed to help format incident descriptions with pre-configured work notes for the most common issues. Also programed to have a separate page that allows the storage of the previously created incident descriptions.

#### Computer Programmer Intern at Budget Ninjas LLC

(July 2018 – October 2019) (Business Closed)

Technologies: Visual Studio, SQL, SSRS, ASP.NET, C#, Telerik, JavaScript, CSS, HTML, Azure Devops

 Completed a number of projects to enhance their website and created an SSRS report for operations.

For more details please visit:

https://mr-bland.github.io/Portfolio-DB/

#### **Education**

<u>Greenville Technical College</u>: Associates degree in Computer Science (spring 2019)

LinkedIn Learning: Completed a number of technical courses.

Bonds Career Center: Technical training from 2015 to 2017